<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cupertino Choraliers</title>
    <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cupertino Choraliers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:30:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupertino-choraliers.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Schedule</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/posts/summer-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 15:30:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/posts/summer-schedule/</guid>
      <description>Hi Choraliers,
Below are the venues and times of our performances. The time given is performance time so plan to arrive the usual 15 minutes or more ahead of time:
 July 8 at 10:30
Cedar Crest Nursing and Rehabilitation
197 E Fremont Ave
Sunnyvale, CA 94087
Map
 July 15 at 10:00
Grace Adult Day Health Care
3010 Olcott St
Santa Clara, CA 95054
Map
 July 22 at 10:30</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 18:15:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The Choraliers started in 1978 as a choral class as part of the “Older Adult Studies” program at De Anza College. The first director was Joan Lomax. The class met at the Cupertino Senior Center and generally kept the same schedule as De Anza College. Joan Lomax retired in the fall of 1997. Laura Green started directing the class in the fall of 1998. In the summer of 2004, De Anza College terminated the Older Adult Studies program because of funding priorities, and in the fall of 2004 the Choraliers was formed as an independent organization with ties to the Fun Times Singers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/contacts/</guid>
      <description>The Director @ 408-250-2449</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Links</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:33:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/links/</guid>
      <description>Learning tracks for all Choraliers music at the Fun Times Singers&amp;rsquo; website (login required)
Choraliers Music Files</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chorus &amp; Group Photos</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/quartets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/quartets/</guid>
      <description>The Choraliers in 2016 
Chocolatiers  
The Chorus during rehearsal in Quinlan Community Center</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director Bio</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/director/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:30:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/director/</guid>
      <description>Director: Laura Green
Laura Green is a composer, choral conductor, Suzuki piano teacher, freelance pianist, and church organist.
Laura is also one-half of a Flute and Piano Duo, the other half is her sister, Allison. Together they play for parties, weddings and corporate events.
Laura directed the Fun Times Singers from 2002 to 2008.
Now Laura directs and accompanies the Choraliers, a group of Seniors (30 people) who provide choral music for retirement facilities and rest homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows &amp; Performances</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/shows/</guid>
      <description>The Choraliers produce a public performance every two or three years.
During the year the Choraliers perform at nursing homes, convalescent homes and retirement homes, these are not public performances..
The new quarter starts on Monday, September 9th.
Summer Session Perfomances  July 15 at 10:00
Grace Adult Day Health Care
3010 Olcott St
Santa Clara, CA 95054
Map
 July 22 at 10:30
Health Care Center at the Forum</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/meetings/</guid>
      <description>The Cupertino Choraliers normally meet at
St Jude’s Episcopal Church
20920 McClellan Road
Cupertino, CA 95014
Map
Every Monday morning at 10:00 AM
The meetings are split up into 4 Quarters.
Winter January to March, Fee $35.00 plus Music.
Spring April to June, Fee $35.00 plus Music.
Summer July to September, Fee $20.00 no new Music.
Fall October to December, Fee TBA plus Music.
All fees are subject to changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Repertoire</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/repertoire_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/repertoire_2/</guid>
      <description> 2019 Holiday Repertoire to be announced. Last years songs    Song Artist(s)     Amani Utupe Patsy Ford Simms   All Aboard Harry Warren/Mack Gordon   Baby is Cold Outside Frank Loesser   Do you Hear What I Hear Noel Regney &amp;amp; Georia Shayne   Dream A Little Dream Of Me Gus Kahn/Fabian Andre &amp;amp; Wilbur Schwandt   Gettin&amp;rsquo; In The Mood For Christmas Joe Garland/Mike Himelstein &amp;amp; Brian Setzer   Got My Love To Keep Me Warm Medley   Holiday Blessing Joyce Eilers   Let Me Entertain You Stephen Sondheim/Jule Styne   Mele Kalikimaka R Alex Andderson   Put On A Happy Face Lee Adams/Charles Strouse   Sentimental Journey Bud Green Les Brown/Ben Homer   Shine On Me Traditional Spiritual   The Christmas Song Mel Torme &amp;amp; Robert Wells   We Need a Little Christmas Jerry Herman   White Christmas Irving Berlin    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular Repertoire</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/repertoire_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:26:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/repertoire_1/</guid>
      <description> Current    Song Artist(s)     All I Have To Do Is Dream Boudleaux &amp;amp; Felice Bryant   All the Things You Are Oscar Hammerstein &amp;amp; Jerome Kern   Amani Utupe Patsy Ford Simms   Ashokan Farewell Grian McGreger &amp;amp; Jay Unger   Camptown Races Stephen Foster   Dream a Little Dream of Me Gus Kahn &amp;amp; Fabian Andrre   Give My Regards To Broadway George M Cohan   I Want To Be Happy Irving Caesar &amp;amp; Vincent Youmans   Let There Be Peace On Earth Sy Miller &amp;amp; Jill Jackson   Old Devil Moon E Y Harburg &amp;amp; Burton Lane   Shalom Jerry Herman   Shenandoah American Folk Song   Shine On Me Traditional Spiritual   Swingin&amp;rsquo; With The Gershwins Georga &amp;amp; Ira Gershwin   Venus Edward Marshall, arr Green   We Love the &amp;lsquo;50s 5 Songs    Other    Song Artist(s)     All Aboard Harry Warren &amp;amp; Mack Gordon   Joy Be With You All Scottish Folk Song   Look To The Rainbow E Y Harburg &amp;amp; Burton Lane    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupertino-choraliers.org/members/</guid>
      <description>The Cupertino Choraliers Director: Laura Green
Sopranos: Kathleen Alexander, Genny Atkinson, Dina Bensen, Shirley Cancellieri, Carol Clark, Lorraine Denenberg, Patty Dick, Barbara Hartson, Alice Kawash, Linda Malmstrom, Margaret McCrary
2nd Sopranos: Wendy DeBevoise, Doris Britschgi, Lynell Cortes, Gayle Frank, Jean Murphy
Altos: Wilma Brisendine, Judy Gregory, Barb Hamer, Shobhana Kavathekar, Marilyn Walthers, Nancy Wood, Susan Zaslaw
Tenors: Sibby Coxhead, Bea Schadle
Bass: Gerry Hanson, John Heather, David Norlander, Ben Roisen, Frank Yap</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>