<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cupertino Choraliers</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cupertino Choraliers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 18:15:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 18:15:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The Choraliers started in 1978 as a choral class as part of the “Older Adult Studies” program at De Anza College. The first director was Joan Lomax. The class met at the Cupertino Senior Center and generally kept the same schedule as De Anza College. Joan Lomax retired in the fall of 1997. Laura Green started directing the class in the fall of 1998. In the summer of 2004, De Anza College terminated the Older Adult Studies program because of funding priorities, and in the fall of 2004 the Choraliers was formed as an independent organization with ties to the Fun Times Singers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contacts/</guid>
      <description>The Director @ 408-247-2809</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Links</title>
      <link>http://example.org/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:33:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/links/</guid>
      <description>Learning tracks for all Choraliers music.
http://funtimessingers.org/index.php?p=cf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chorus &amp; Group Photos</title>
      <link>http://example.org/quartets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/quartets/</guid>
      <description> The Choraliers in 2016 Chocolatiers The Chorus during rehearsal in Quinlan Community Center </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director Bio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/director/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:30:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/director/</guid>
      <description>Director: Laura Green
Laura Green is a composer, choral conductor, Suzuki piano teacher, freelance pianist, and church organist.
Laura is also one-half of a Flute and Piano Duo, the other half is her sister, Allison. Together they play for parties, weddings and corporate events.
Laura directed the Fun Times Singers from 2002 to 2008.
Now Laura directs the Choraliers, a group of Seniors (40 people) who provide sing-a-longs for retirement facilities and rest homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows &amp; Performances</title>
      <link>http://example.org/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/shows/</guid>
      <description>The Choraliers produce a public performance every two or three years, the next performance will be in 2019 or 2020.
During the year the Choraliers perform at nursing homes, convalescent homes and retirement homes, these are not public performances..
The new quarter starts on Monday, January 4th
Please note that all rehearsals will be held at
St. Jude’s Episcopal Church
20920 McClellan Road
Cupertino, CA 95014
408-252-4166
Winter season 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/meetings/</guid>
      <description>The Cupertino Choraliers normally meet at
St. Jude’s Episcopal Church
20920 McClellan Road
Cupertino, CA 95014
Every Monday morning at 10:00 AM
The meetings are split up into 4 Quarters.
Winter January to March, Fee $40.00 plus Music.
Spring April to June, Fee $25.00 No new Music.
Summer July to September, Fee $40.00 plus Music.
Fall October to December, Fee $40.00 plus Music.
During the Fall Quarter we perform Christmas Music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Repertoire</title>
      <link>http://example.org/repertoire_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/repertoire_2/</guid>
      <description>   Song Artist(s)     Amani Utupe Patsy Ford Simms   All Aboard Harry Warren/Mack Gordon   Baby is Cold Outside Frank Loesser   Do you Hear What I Hear Noel Regney &amp;amp; Georia Shayne   Dream A Little Dream Of Me Gus Kahn/Fabian Andre &amp;amp; Wilbur Schwandt   Gettin&amp;rsquo; In The Mood For Christmas Joe Garland/Mike Himelstein &amp;amp; Brian Setzer   Got My Love To Keep Me Warm Medley   Holiday Blessing Joyce Eilers   Let Me Entertain You Stephen Sondheim/Jule Styne   Mele Kalikimaka R Alex Andderson   Put On A Happy Face Lee Adams/Charles Strouse   Sentimental Journey Bud Green Les Brown/Ben Homer   Shine On Me Traditional Spiritual   The Christmas Song Mel Torme &amp;amp; Robert Wells   We Need a Little Christmas Jerry Herman   White Christmas Irving Berlin    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular Repertoire</title>
      <link>http://example.org/repertoire_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:26:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/repertoire_1/</guid>
      <description>   Song Artist(s)     Amani Utupe Patsy Ford Simms   All Aboard Harry Warren &amp;amp; Mack Gordon   All I Have To Do Is Dream Boudleaux &amp;amp; Felice Bryant   All the Things You Are Oscar Hammerstein &amp;amp; Jerome Kern   Ashokan Farewell Grian McGreger &amp;amp; Jay Unger   Camptown Races Stephen Foster   Dream a Little Dream of Me Gus Kahn &amp;amp; Fabian Andrre   Give My Regards To Broadway George M Cohan   I Want To Be Happy Irving Caesar &amp;amp; Vincent Youmans   Joy Be With You All Scottish Folk Song   Let There Be Peace On Earth Sy Miller &amp;amp; Jill Jackson   Look To The Rainbow E Y Harburg &amp;amp; Burton Lane   Old Devil Moon E Y Harburg &amp;amp; Burton Lane   Shalom Jerry Herman   Sentimental Journey Bud Green &amp;amp; Ben Homer   Shenandoah American Folk Song   Shine On Me Traditional Spiritual   Swingin&amp;rsquo; With The Gershwins Georga &amp;amp; Ira Gershwin   We Love the ‘50s 5 Songs    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>http://example.org/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/members/</guid>
      <description>The Cupertino Choraliers Director: Laura Green
Sopranos: Kathleen Alexander, Genny Atkinson, Dina Bensen, Shirley Cancellieri, Carol Clark, Lorraine Denenberg, Patty Dick, Barbara Hartson, Alice Kawash, Linda Malmstrom, Margaret McCrary
2nd Sopranos: Wendy DeBevoise, Doris Britschgi, Lynell Cortes, Gayle Frank, Jean Murphy
Altos: Wilma Brisendine, Anne Chiang, Judy Gregory, Barb Hamer, Shobhana Kavathekar, Marilyn Walthers, Nancy Wood, Susan Zaslaw
Tenors: Sibby Coxhead, Bea Schadle
Bass: Gerry Hanson, John Heather, David Norlander, Ben Roisen, Frank Yap</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer News</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/summer-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 15:30:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/summer-news/</guid>
      <description>This where periodic news updates can go.
Technical stuff below.
Below are some examples of Markdown to see how it is rendered in the browser.
http://example.org/posts/ H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Alternatively, for H1 and H2, an underline-ish style:
Alt-H1 Alt-H2 Emphasis, aka italics, with asterisks or underscores.
Strong emphasis, aka bold, with asterisks or underscores.
Combined emphasis with asterisks and underscores.
Strikethrough uses two tildes. Scratch this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>